- 嘿 你准备好要走了吗？ - 让我先把这个完成
- You ready to go?     - Let me just finish this.
嘿 罗斯 瞧
Hey, Ross. Check this out.
我就是做不好
Yeah, I can't do that. Heh.
- 你在做什么呢？ - 你有看过这个吗？
- What are you doing?     - Have you seen this?
这是我们大学校友会的新网站
It's our new alumni website for college.
你可以留言给大家 让大家知道你的近况
You can post messages for people, let everyone know what you're up to.
喔 太好了 一个更快速方式 去告诉大家 我失业又没小孩
Oh, great. A faster way to tell people that I'm unemployed and childless.
知道大家在做什么 真有趣
It's actually interesting to find out what people are doing.
记得艾卓雅里奇吗？
Remember Andrea Rich?
- 不肯跟你上床的那个高个子女生吗？ - 嗯
- Tall girl, wouldn't sleep with you?     - Uh-huh.
她的网络公司倒了 而且在一次划船意外中失去一只耳朵
Well, her Internet company went under, and she lost an ear in a boating accident.
我敢说她现在一定会跟你上床了
Bet she'd sleep with you now.
才不 我已经寄电邮问过她了
No, I already e-mailed her.
让我看看你是怎么写自己的
Let me see what you wrote about yourself.
- 喔   - "古生物学博士 有两个小孩"
- Oh.     -"Doctor of paleontology, two kids."
等等 你跟卡萝分开的原因 是因为兴趣不同吗？
Wait a second. You split with Carol because you had different interests?
我认为你跟她分开的原因 是因为就是有相同的兴趣
I think you split with Carol because you had one very similar interest.
我等一下再写好了 让我拿一件外套
You know what? I'm gonna finish this later, okay? Let me just grab my coat.
好的
Okay.
怎样？你认为你花两分钟 就能学会吗？
What, did you think you learned how to do it in the last two minutes?
或许我们可以帮他完成
Maybe we finish this for him.
同时 我在实验室里复制了一只恐龙
Also, I cloned a dinosaur in my lab.
她现在是我的女朋友了
She is now my girlfriend.
我不在乎社会的眼光 这是我们拥有最完美的性爱
I don't care what society says, it's the best sex I've ever had.
- 然后 寄出   - 不 你不可以这样
- And send.     - No, no... You can't do that to him.
- 好了 我们走   - 老兄
- All right, let's go.     - Dude!
我想你很清楚的证明了 不能让你在室内抱着球
Uh, I think you made it clear you can't be trusted with the ball inside the house.
然后 寄出
And send.
嘿 篮球好玩吗？
Hey. How was basketball?
很好玩 一直玩到钱德的眼睛 被手指戳到
It was fun. Right up until Chandler got a finger in the eye.
喔 天啊 是谁弄的？
Oh, no. Who did that?
钱德自己
Chandler.
嘿
Yeah.
- 瑞秋   - 怎样？
- Rash?     - Yeah?
哈吉为什么在艾玛的婴儿车里呢？
What's Huggsy doing in the crib with Emma?
她在到处爬的时候抓到他
She was just crawling around and she found him...
所以我就让她跟他一起睡
so I just let her sleep with him.
- 没关系吧？ - 当然 没关系
- That's all right, isn't it?     - Of course. Yeah.
只是填充玩具 你知道的 是给小孩玩的 不是给大人的
It's a stuffed animal, you know? It's for kids. Not for adults.
这点我知道
I know that.
乔伊 你确定吗？我知道你很爱他
Joey, you're sure? I mean, I know how much you love him.
瑞秋 让我们说清楚好吗？我没有爱哈吉
Rachel, let's be clear on this, okay? I do not love Huggsy.
我只是以正常的程度喜欢他
I like him a normal amount.
好吧 但是艾玛爱死他了
All right. Well, Emma loves him.
是啊 为何不呢？他是那么的美好
Yeah. Well, why wouldn't she? He's a wonderful person.
- 嗨   - 嘿 菲比 你还好吗？
- Hi.     - Hey, Phoebe. How you doing?
- 你感觉好点了吗？ - 分手真是难受
- You feeling better?     - Breaking up sucks.
- 喔 我真的好想麦克   - 喔 真抱歉
- Oh, I really miss Mike.     - Oh, I'm so sorry.
我已经试过所有疗伤法了 我甚至还尝试要写首歌
I've tried everything to feel better. I even tried writing a song about it...
但是我不想出任何可以配这个调的…
but I can't think of anything that rhymes with:
嘿 摩妮卡 我需要你帮我度过这段时期
Hey, Monica, I'm gonna need your help getting through this.
你是说你不需要我帮忙吗？
You're saying you're not gonna need my help?
不 当我准备好要听…
No. When I get to the point where I'm ready...
挨死的麦克笑话时 我会来找你的
to hear cruel, mocking jokes about Mike, I'm gonna come to you.
很好 因为我已经想出三个了 四个 我刚刚又想出第四个
Oh, good, because I've already thought of three. Four! I just thought of a fourth.
好了 我知道我的决定是正确的
Okay. I mean, I know I did the right thing.
麦克永远都不想要结婚
Mike never wants to get married...
而我也不应该经营一段没有未来的感情
and I shouldn't be in a relationship that has no future.
但是很快的 我会很想念他
But pretty soon, I'm gonna miss him so much...
我会想再见到他 你一定要阻止我
I'm gonna want to see him again, and you have to stop me.
好的 没问题
Okay, you got it.
除非… 我是不是想太多了呢？
Unless... Am I being too crazy about this?
好吧 就算没有未来又如何
All right, so, you know, there's no future.
那不表示我们不能玩一玩啊
But that doesn't mean we still can't have fun.
- 你知道吗？忘了我刚刚说的   - 真的吗？
- You know what? Forget what I said.     - Really?
- 好吧 如果你那样想的话   - 那是个测试 你没过关
- All right, if that's what you want.     - That was a test, and you just failed.
该死的 新手失误
Damn it! Rookie mistake.
我跟恐龙做爱？
I have sex with dinosaurs?
我确定我好像在哪看过耶
I believe I read that somewhere.
不只不好笑 而且根本不可能 好吗？
Not only is it not funny, it's physically impossible. Okay?
由于物种不同 我必须要有六吸长的… 不好笑
Depending on the species, I'd have to have a 6-foot-long... It's not funny!
我真心表示无法赞同
I respectfully disagree.
不敢相信你会在 我的校友网页上那样写
I can't believe you put that on my alumni page.
- 谁在乎呢？有谁会去看啊   - 你最好是希望没有
- Who cares? Nobody reads those.     - You better hope not...
因为我刚刚就看到 你网页上的一些讯息
because I just read what you put on your page.
- 我没有网页   - 喔 我真心表示无法赞同
- I don't have a page.     - Oh, I respectfully disagree!
瞧瞧你 甜美又天真的样子 睡得跟天使一样
Look at you. All sweet and innocent, sleeping like an angel.
还有艾玛那只肥肥的小手抱住你
With Emma's chubby little hands wrapped around you.
没关系 艾玛 你继续睡
It's okay, Emma. You stay asleep.
不要靠近婴儿床 我有武器
Step away from the crib! I have a weapon!
没关系 没关系 瑞秋 是我 把发卷放下来
It's okay! It's okay, Rach! It's me! Put down the scrunchie.
- 你在做什么？ - 喔 我听到艾玛的声音
- What are you doing?     - Well, I heard Emma stirring...
所以我过来确定一下 让她可以抓到哈吉
so I came in to make sure she could reach Huggsy.
谢谢 既然我已经醒了 我要去上厕所
Oh. Oh, thanks. All right, well, now that I'm up, I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
好的 拿去 亲爱的
Okay, there you go, sweetie.
我们还没完
This isn't over.
等等 为什么罗斯 要跟你班上每个人说…
Wait a second. Why would Ross tell everyone in your class...
你是"同志到不能再同志了"呢？
that you are "as gay as the day is long"?
因为我告诉大家说 他跟恐龙上床
Because I told everyone he slept with dinosaurs.
那很明显是个笑话 但是这个很有可能是真的
Well, that's clearly a joke. This could easily be true.
拜托你去接好吗？我整天一直接到大家恭喜我的电话
Would you get that, please? People have been calling to congratulate me all day.
喂？
Hello?
不 他不在家 我是他老婆
No, he's not here. Yeah, this is his wife.
是啊 我也被吓了好大一跳
Yeah. Well, it came as quite a shock to me too.
嗯 我早就该猜到了
Well, I guess I should've known. Yeah.
他总是强迫我看《红磨坊》
He just kept making me watch Moulin Rouge.
挂掉 挂掉
Hang up- Hang UP-
那是部好电影
And that was a great movie.
我一定会报复罗斯的
I'm so gonna get back at Ross.
喔 是的 这会让他好看 来吧
Oh, yeah, this'll show him. Here we go.
- 你在做什么呢？ - 喔 你等着看吧 我的朋友
- What are you doing?     - Oh, you'll see, my friend!
我死了？
I'm dead?
英年早逝
And so young.
公告我死了？这一点都不好笑
Posting that I died? That really isn't funny.
你怎么死的比较好笑
Well, how you died was funny.
拜托 被飞船撞死？
Oh, please. Hit by a blimp?
那每年都会杀死一个美国人
It kills over one Americans every year.
难以置信 我同学们会以为我死了
Unbelievable. My classmates are gonna think I'm dead.
我的教授 我父母会接到许多电话的
My professors. My parents are gonna get phone calls.
你在玩弄大家的情感
You're messing with people's feelings here.
你要谈大家的情感是吗？
You wanna talk about people's feelings?
你应该知道当我昨天告诉史登教授…
You should have heard how hurt Professor Stern was...
不能跟他一起去度假时 他有多受伤
when I told him I wouldn't be able to go with him to Key West!
你真的太过分了 但是没关系
You've really crossed a line here. But that's okay.
因为我要去买影像处理软体
Because I'm on my way to buy some Photoshop software...
和一叠的同志色情照片
and a stack of gay porn.
没错 你的出柜将会是图文并茂
That's right. Your coming-out is about to get real graphic!
天啊 我真希望麦克在这里
God, I wish Mike were here.
好了 如果麦克在这里 你们要做什么呢？
Okay, if Mike were here, what would the two of you be doing?
你们是动物吗？现在才下午四点耶
What are you, animals? It's 4:00 in the afternoon.
我得打电话给他 只是跟他说说话 应该不会怎样
I gotta call him. Just to talk to him. There's no harm in that.
菲比 事情都是那样开始的
Phoebe, that's how it starts.
"我不需要吃蛋糕 我只要闻一闻…
"I don't need to eat the cake, I'll just smell the icing.
那么 一点点就好"或是 "好吧 一小片就好"
Why not just a little sliver?" Or, "Okay, just a slice or two."
接下来一下子你就210磅了
You know, the next thing you know, you're 210 pounds...
而你连进门都会被卡住
and you get wedged in going down the tunnel slide.
菲比 亲爱的 我知道这很难
Phoebe, honey, I know this is hard.
但是如果你跟他说话 然后你就会想见他了
But look, if you talk to him, then you're gonna want to see him.
而如果你见了他 你就会想跟他复合了
And if you see him, you're gonna wanna get back together.
我知道 那不是你想要的
And I know that's not what you want.
好了 把电话给我
All right, so give me your phone.
- 拿去   - 感谢
- Here.     - Thank you.
- 还有你的手机   - 好吧
- And now your cell.     - Okay.
拿去
There you go.
- 这是你的手机？ - 是啊
- This is your cell phone?     - Yes.
这是你目前在用的手机？
This is your current cell phone?
是的 它让我想起简单的时日
Yes. It reminds me of a simpler time.
菲比？你的皮包呢？
Phoebe? Where's your purse?
- 嘿 不行   - 不
- Hey! No!     - No!
- 给我   - 不给你
- Give it to me!     - You can't have it.
- 给我   - 不要
- Give it to me!     - No.
- 我会伸进去拿的   - 喔 是喔
- I'll go in there.     - Oh, yeah.
- 菲比 过来   - 不
- Come here!     - No!
- 给我   - 你疯了
- Give it to me!     - You're crazy! God.
啊哈
Aha!
去你的 摩妮卡盖勒宾
Damn you, Monica Geller hyphen Bing!
嘿 瞧瞧是谁来了 是乔伊 而且他带新朋友来了
Hey, look who's here. It's Joey. And he brought home a friend.
艾玛在这里
Joey, Emma's right here.
你答应不会在白天 带女生回来的
You promised not to bring girls home in the middle of the day anymore.
不 不 不 不是女生 是…
No, no, no, it's not a girl. It's...
- 全新的哈吉   - 哦
- a brand-new Huggsy!     - Oh.
喔 这真是太棒了 现在艾玛有两个哈吉了
Oh, that's so great. Now Emma has two Huggsies.
不 不 喔不 不 艾玛只有一个哈吉
No, no. Oh, no. No, Emma has one Huggsy.
新的哈吉
The new Huggsy. Huh?
另外那个哈吉 我不知道 我想我就拿回来好了
The other Huggsy, I don't know, I guess I'll just take him back.
你知道吗？当我还是小女孩时 我有一只粉红色小马 叫小棉花
You know what? When I was a little girl, I had a little pink pony named Cotton.
喔 我好爱她 去哪我都带着她 我会梳她的尾巴…
Oh, I loved her so much. I took her everywhere. I would braid her tail...
快点移交吧
Make the transfer!
旧哈吉身上有个钮扣不见了 我找不到 有没有关系？
Should I be concerned that a button fell off the old Huggsy and I can't find it?
不 不用担心 很多年前被我吞下去了 嘿
Don't worry about it. I swallowed that years ago. Hey.
喔 怎么了？我想她不喜欢新哈吉
Oh, what? I don't think she likes the new Huggsy.
- 但他是- 样的啊   - 我想她要旧的哈吉
- But he's the same.     - I think she wants the old one back.
- 是喔 但他们一模一样啊   - 乔伊 拿来
- Yeah, but he's the same.     - Joey, come on.
根本是一样的嘛
But he's the same.
你不一样
You're not the same.
啊哈
Aha!
你这样吓不到我…
You know, it's a lot less surprising to do that...
因为是我按开楼下的门让你进来的
after I've buzzed you into the building.
菲比 为什么门边有男人的鞋子呢？
So, Phoebe, why are there men's shoes by the door?
- 那是我的鞋子   - 喔
- Those are my shoes.     - Oh.
当你复元之后 我们一定要去血拼
Well, when you get over this breakup, we need to go shopping.
听着 摩妮卡 我真的很感激你这样关心我
Look, Monica, I really appreciate you checking in on me.
- 但是我已经觉得好多了   - 真的？
- But I'm actually feeling a lot better.     - You are?
是的 我只是有点想自己独处
Yeah, I just kind of want to be alone right now.
- 是谁啊？ - 我叫了中餐外送
- Who's that?     - I ordered Chinese food.
真是太巧了
What are the chances?
在十亿的中国人当中 他们竟然派麦克来
One billion Chinese people, and they send Mike!
- 你来这里做什么呢？ - 菲比打电话给我
- What are you doing here?     - Phoebe called me.
- 菲比   - 我很抱歉 我受不了
- Phoebe!     - I'm sorry. I broke down.
我想要见他
I wanted to see him.
该死的 菲比 你是怎么打电话给他的？
Damn it, Phoebe, how did you even call him?
电话主机有免持听筒功能
There's a speakerphone on the base unit.
主机 用脑啊 摩妮卡 用用脑
Base unit. Think, Monica, think!
- 听着 如果我想见菲比 而她…   - 这不关你的事
- Look, if I want to see Phoebe, and she...     - This doesn't concern you.
对不起 我只是听到有人提到我的名字
Sorry. I guess I was thrown off by the mention of my name.
听着 你们不能这样做
Look, guys, you can't do this.
这会使事情更复杂的
It's gonna make getting over each other harder.
如果什么事都没发生就不会 我们不能就当朋友吗？
Not if nothing happens. Why can't we just hang out as friends?
当然可以 如果你们只是朋友 那我也可以加入你们
Sure. If you're just gonna hang out as friends, then maybe I'll join you.
你知道的 我是你的朋友 也是麦克的朋友
I'm your friend and Mike's friend.
是的
Well...
坐下吧
Sit down.
让个位置给你们的朋友
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa. Make room for your friend.
- 你过得好不好？ - 我还挺不错的
- So how have you been?     - I've been pretty good.
- 你真的很美   - 谢谢 你看起来也不错
- You look really beautiful.     - Thanks. You look good too.
不对 这太危险了 放干净点
No, no, no. This is dangerous territory. Keep it clean.
那钢琴演奏还好吗？
So how's the piano playing going?
事实上 我最近弹了许多情歌
Actually, I've been playing a lot of love songs lately.
- 我一直很想你   - 我也是
- I've missed you.     - I've missed you too.
在我要过来这里的路上 我看到一个酒鬼吐了一地
You know, on the way over here, I saw this drunk guy throw up.
然后一只鸽子还去吃
And then a pigeon ate it.
嘿 罗斯
Hey. Ross.
听着 我只是想过来跟你道歉
Look, I just wanted to apologize.
别告诉我你真的在做我的同志照
Don't tell me you actually made those gay pictures of me.
瞧瞧这个
Uh-huh, uh-huh. Check this out.
所以如果我有健身 看起来就会是这样
So that's what I'd look like if I worked out.
而且还有警察先生为我服务
And was being serviced by a policeman.
你不是真的要贴出这些照片吧？
You're not gonna actually send these out, are you?
事实上 我没有必要 因为你"罗斯死了"的笑话根本没用
Actually, I don't need to, because your little "Ross is dead" joke didn't work.
好吗？根本就没有人回应
Okay? There were no responses.
没有人张贴任何东西 没有人打电话给我父母
Nobody posted anything on the website, nobody called my parents...
你才好笑
so the joke, my friend, is on you.
没有人来电 没有人写什么 没有人在乎我死了
Nobody called, nobody wrote anything, nobody cares that I'm dead.
喔 我的天
Oh, my God.
- 没人在乎我死了吗？ - 喔 别这样 你知道不是那样的
- Nobody cares that I'm dead?     - Oh, come on, you know that's not true.
你在说什么呢？你有六十个回复…
What are you talking about? You get 60 responses...
只不过是因为出柜而已
just for coming out of the closet.
而我死了 却连一个回复都没有
I didn't get one response, and I'm dead!
嗯 同志社团比死人社团还要活跃
Well, the gay community is a lot more vocal than the dead community.
我不敢相信 连我地质学伴都没有回复 以前都是我罩他的
I can't believe this. Not even my geology lab partner. And I carried that guy.
听着 我们不要再多想了 好吗？
All right. Look, let's think about this, okay?
你认为大家会想要在 这悲伤的时刻打扰你的家人吗？
You think people are gonna disturb your family at this tragic time?
有人会在网站上张贴哀悼辞吗？
That people are gonna post condolences on a website?
不是说大家不在乎
This isn't about people not caring that you're dead.
而是那并非适合的抒发悲情的管道
This is about people not having a decent outlet for their grief.
- 你说的没错 那不是适合的管道   - 没错
- You're right. There isn't a decent outlet.     - Right.
我确定如果你有举办追悼会
Come on. I'm sure if you had a funeral or memorial service...
一定会有很多人来的
tons of people would come.
没错
Exactly!
罗斯 你要干嘛？
Ross, what are you doing?
你要帮自己办追悼会？
You're having a memorial service for yourself?
不 那会太离谱了 你要帮我办
No, that would be stupid. You're having it for me.
- 罗斯 不要寄出 不要寄…   - 不 太迟了 寄出了
- Ross, don't press send. Don't press...     - No, too late. Too late. It's sent.
对不起 还有你 跟警察先生的照片也寄了
Sorry, so is that picture of you and the policeman.
我刚要哄艾玛睡一下 你有看到哈吉吗？
I'm trying to put Emma down for a nap. Have you seen Huggsy?
原版的还是烂的？
Uh, original or crappy?
- 原版的   - 没有 抱歉 没有看到
- Original.     - No. Sorry. Haven't seen him.
那你床上突起来的是什么？
Then what's that big lump under your covers'?
- 是摩妮卡 好吗？ - 那不是摩妮卡
- It's Monica, okay?     - That's not Monica!
好啦 没关系 是原版的哈吉
All right, fine! It's original Huggsy!
我知道艾玛要他 但他是我的 而我需要他
I know Emma wants him, but he's mine and I need him.
她真是不讲道理
She's being unreasonable.
乔伊 艾玛爱那个蠢企鹅是有原因的
Joey, there is a reason that Emma loves that stupid penguin so much!
喔 不要捣住他的耳朵
Oh, don't cover its ears!
因为他让她想起她的乔伊叔叔
It's because it reminds her of her Uncle Joey.
- 真的？ - 是的
- It does?     - Yeah.
她很喜欢他是因为 她是那么爱她的乔伊叔叔
And she's comforted by him because she loves her Uncle Joey so much.
- 真的？她爱我？ - 喔 是的
- Really? She loves me?     - Oh, yeah.
但是你知道吗？如果你需要哈吉 没关系
But you know what? If you need Huggsy, don't worry.
艾玛会谅解的 我不会 但是那又如何呢
Emma will totally understand. I won't, but whatever.
好的 等等 瑞秋 我是说如果…
Okay, wait a minute, wait a minute, Rach. I mean, if...
如果艾玛那么喜欢哈吉 那么…
If Huggsy means that much to Emma, then...
嗯 就给她吧
Well, she can have him.
喔 亲爱的 我就知道乔伊叔叔最好了
Oh, sweet, I knew Uncle Joey would step up.
- 艾玛 瞧是谁回来了   - 不 算了 算了 我做不到
- Look, Emma. Look who's back.     - No, forget it! Forget it! I can't do it!
你…你要把哈吉从一个小孩手上抢走？
Are you...? You're gonna take Huggsy away from a little child?
要不然你认为我当初怎么拿到哈吉的？
How do you think I got him in the first place?
好了 你们两个 我要去上厕所
All right, you two. I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
我不希望在我离开时 发生什么事
I don't want anything going on while I'm gone.
有几件事你们可以讨论
Here's a few things you can discuss:
黏液 菌类 还有我跟罗斯如何把玩这些东西
Mucus, fungus, and the idea of me and Ross doing it.
我真的好想你
I've missed you so much.
我不会要求你复合 我知道我们要的是不同的东西 但…
I'm not gonna ask you to get back together. I know we want different things, but...
- 只要跟你再共度- 晚就好   - 我也想要
- Just to be with you one more night.     - I want that too.
- 但那不是会使事情更困难吗？ - 再不会比现在更困难了
- But is that gonna make it too hard?     - It can't be any harder than this.
如果我知道上一次见到你 就是最后一次 我…
I mean, if I had known the last time I saw you would be the last time, I...
我一定会努力记住你的脸 你的一举一动
I would have stopped to memorize your face, the way you moved.
你的一切
Everything about you.
如果我知道上次亲吻你 就是最后一次…
If I had known the last time I kissed you would be the last time...
我就不会停下来
I never would have stopped.
亲啊 你这个傻瓜
Kiss him, you fool!
- 什么？ - 你没有听到他说什么吗？
- What?     - Didn't you hear that speech?
如果你不亲他 我来亲
If you don't kiss him, then I will.
我好想你
I missed you so much.
- 我就知道你在这里   - 妈的
- I knew you'd be here!     - Aw, crap.
- 他是谁？ - 我朋友曼尼
- Who is this?     - It's my friend Manny.
我请他看好我 远离你
I asked him to keep me away from you.
- 我也在帮菲比做同样的事   - 那你根本没做好你工作
- Hey, that's what I'm doing for Phoebe.     - Well, you're not doing a very good job.
- 什么？ - 亲吻是怎么回事呢？
- Excuse me?     - What's with the kissing?
嘿 至少我也在现场哪
Hey, at least I knew where my guy was.
是啊 感谢上帝 你在这里监看他们亲吻
Yeah, thank God you were here to oversee all the kissing.
- 你没有听到他说的话   - 我听到了
- You didn't hear the speech. MANNY: I've heard the speech.
如果他知道那是最后一次…
If he knew it was gonna be the last time...
嘿 那很令人感动 你真是没心肝
Hey, it was very moving. You're just heartless!
- 你太软弱了   - 你太奇怪了
- You're weak!     - You're weird!
- 你裤子拉链没拉   - 噢
- Your pants are undone.     - Oh!
他们去哪儿了呢？
Where'd they go?
- 该死的   - 我们搞砸了
- Damn it.     - Well, we blew it.
我只能怪我自己
I blame myself.
而我也只能怪你
And I blame you too.
已经一个小时了 而我同学竟然一个都没来？
It's been an hour, and not one of my classmates has shown up?
我告诉你 要是我真的死了 有些人一定会被鬼缠死的
I tell you, when I actually die, some people are gonna get seriously haunted.
来了 有人来了
There you go. Someone came.
好了 好了 我要去躲起来了
Okay. Okay. I'm gonna go hide.
真是兴奋 我第一个追悼者
This is so exciting. My first mourner!
嗨 很高兴你能够来
Hi. Glad you could come.
- 请进   - 嗨 你是钱德宾吗？
- Please come in.     - Hi. You're Chandler Bing, right?
我是汤姆高登 是你班上的同学
I'm Tom Gordon. I was in your class.
喔 是的 是的 让我帮你拿外套
Oh, yes. Yes, let me take your coat.
谢谢 很难过听到罗斯的事 真是…
Thanks. Uh, I'm so sorry about Ross, it's...
没关系 至少他死时正在做喜欢的事
No, at least he died doing what he loved.
看飞船
Watching blimps.
- 那是谁？ - 你认识- 个叫汤姆高登的吗？
- Who is it?     - You know some guy, Tom Gordon?
我不记得他了
I don't remember him.
但是 我启发过太多人了
But then again, I touched so many lives.
那你跟罗斯很熟吗？
So did you know Ross well?
事实上我不太认识他 我来是因为听到钱德的事
Actually, I barely knew him. I came because I heard Chandler's news.
你知道他有在跟谁交往吗？
Do you know if he's seeing anyone?
- 是的 他有 就是我   - 什么？你是说…
- Yes, he is. Me.     - What? You mean...? Oh.
我可以问你一个私人问题吗？你是怎么将胡子刮得这么干净的？
Can I ask you a personal question? How do you shave your beard so close'?
好了 汤姆 你哀悼得够了
Okay, Tommy! That's enough mourning for you.
走吧 再见 好了
Here we go. Bye-bye. All right.
- 嘿 听着 打电话给我   - 好的
- Hey, listen. Call me.     - Okay.
- 我死了却没有人在乎？ - 我看起来像男人吗？
- I'm dead and no one cares?     - I look like a man?
拜托 一次一个荒谬的问题就好
Please, one ridiculous problem at a time.
这并不荒谬 瞧瞧四周 根本没有人来
This isn't ridiculous. Look around, no one's here.
你才通知他们一天而已 又不是每个人天天都上网
You gave them one day's notice. Not everyone checks the website every day.
还有摩妮卡 或许是因为你的站相
And Monica, it's probably the way you stand!
我猜你说的对 但是 总该要有人看到啊
I guess you're right. Still, somebody must have seen it.
我读那所学校四年了 而我竟然没有影响到任何人？
I mean, I went to that school for four years and I didn't have an impact on anyone?
嗯 不是那样的 你有影响到我
Well, that's not true. You had an impact on me.
我是说 已经十五年了 而我们依然是最要好的朋友
I mean, it's 15 years later and we're still best friends.
那不算什么吗？
Doesn't that count for something?
太好了 更多狂野男孩来找钱德了
Oh, great, more party boys for Chandler.
我敢说一定是来看你的 去躲起来
I'm sure it's somebody for you. Now go hide.
嗨 我来参加罗斯盖勒的追悼会
Hi. I'm here for Ross Geller's memorial service.
- 可苗？可苗薇丝顿？ - 是的
- Kori? Kori Weston?     - Yeah.
- 你看起来真棒   - 你是谁呢？
- You look amazing.     - And you are?
钱德 钱德宾 而且我不是同志 我一点都不是
Chandler. Chandler Bing. And I'm not gay. I'm not gay at all.
但是你已经结婚了
You are married, though.
别听他说 他只是心情很差
Don't listen to him. He's in a really bad mood.
我不敢相信罗斯已经走了 真是难过
I can't believe that Ross is gone. It is just so sad.
我不知道罗斯跟你很熟
I didn't know Ross and you were so close.
喔 并没有 但是我们一起上过一堂课 他是个很棒的人
Oh, we weren't. But we had one class together. He was such a great guy.
而且他总是很热情地讨论科学
And he talked so passionately about science.
- 我一直记得他   - 我确定这对他的意义深远
- I always remembered him.     - I'm sure that would mean a lot to him.
而且如果天堂有一扇门
And if heaven has a door...
我敢说他一定耳朵贴着门仔细在听
I'm sure he's pressing his ear up against it and listening intently.
我好多次都想打电话约他出去
I thought so many times about calling him and asking him out.
我想我真的再也没有机会了
I guess I really missed my chance.
不 你还有机会
No, you didn't!
我还活着
I'm still alive!
可苗 我知道这件事让你很惊讶
Kori, I know this is a big surprise for you.
说来话长 但是你刚说的话 让我这一天变得很美好
It's a long story. But the things you just said really made my day.
你的到来真是对我意义重大
The fact that you're here means more to me...
比房间都充满了人还要好
than if this room were filled with people.
你这变态的怪物 谁会做这种事？
You sick freak! Who does that?
我不敢相信我喜欢过你
I can't believe I had a crush on you.
你们有听到吗？
Did you hear that?
可苗薇丝顿喜欢过我
Kori Weston had a crush on me!
没啦 妈 我没死
No, Mom, I am not dead.
我知道这是不可以开玩笑的
I know it's not something to kid about.
这只是我跟钱德在玩的恶作剧 已经结束了 好吗？
It was just a practical joke between Chandler and me, but it's over, okay?
事实上不会的 即使我死了 你也不会没有孩子
Actually, no. Even if I had died, you would not be left childless.
摩妮卡不算吗？
Monica?